{
    "id": "6b067ce0d98b486fbaa6718062a12f51",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Though she studied well ………………… she failed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "but",
                "and",
                "yet"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She is as beautiful ……………… her mother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "so",
                "than"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She is not ………………….. brilliant as her sister.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "so",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He was busy …………………. he was on tour.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "why",
                "then"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Shakespeare was ………………… a poet but also a dramatist.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "not only",
                "both",
                "not just"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He fell asleep ………………….. he was reading the book.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "while"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I would like to go ………………… I am too busy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "but",
                "or",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You can …………………. walk or go by bus.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "neither",
                "nor"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He tried his best ………………… failed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "so",
                "but"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She is neither Sita ………………… Radha.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "or",
                "nor"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}